Guide to the Stanford Student Demonstrations Collection SC0376
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford student demonstrations collection
1970
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University
SC0376
1 Linear Feet
Photographs, lists, memoranda, affidavits, and miscellaneous notes pertaining to participants in campus demonstrations during the spring of 1970; these records were possibly assembled to provide evidence for legal action against the participants by the University.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research.
Description of the Collection
Photographs, lists, memoranda, affidavits, and miscellaneous notes pertaining to participants in campus demonstrations during the spring of 1970; these records were possibly assembled to provide evidence for legal action against the participants by the University.
Students -- Political activity.; Photoprints.; Pitzer, Kenneth S.; Spruill, Warren H.; Bulkeley, Peter Z.; Creighton, Kenneth D.; Stanford University; Valentine, Paul.; Benton, Lee.
- Photographs (Box 1)
- Microfilm (Box 2)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH.2015-062
  - Vietnam Newsletter: Hypocrisy in High Places, 5 Dec 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Meeting on SRI-Research, 14 Apr 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Grindstone, 30 Nov 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Proposed Program for Stanford Faculty, Feb 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Industrial Park, 20 Feb 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Stanford Portfolio, 22 Feb 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The United States in Vietnam - Stanford War Crimes Study Group, Mar 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - FMC: Growth of a Conglomerate, Apr 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The New Man in the New China, May 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - From Our Past, Oct 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - SWOPSI, Winter 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Workshop on Political and Social Issues, Spring 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Times - clippings, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Might vs Right in America, 20-23 Feb 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Radical Teacher, Dec 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - From Our Own Backyard, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - South Africa Catalyst Project, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - What is a SWOPSI?, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Stanford: Where War and Business Meet, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Issues Raised by Franklin Case, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Promised Land - A Grass Roots Report on Mid-Peninsula Land Use, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - References, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Fire and Sandstone, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Operation Dig-In, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)